Guide to the Nicholas School of the Environment Records, 1916-ongoing UA.18.01.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- UA2018.0076
  - Marguerite Kent Repass Ocean Conservation Center dedication photographs, 2006; 73 files; approximatley 275 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0019, Box 44)
  - Marine Lab 70th Anniversary Event, 2010; 315 files; approximately 775 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0011, Box 44)
  - Marine Lab Weekend digital photographs, 2004; 564 files; approximately 2 gigabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0029, UA18-01-0001-OP-0030, and UA18-01-0001-OP-0031, Box 44)
  - Midway Trip- Student Videos, 2011; 14 files; approximately 1 gigabyte. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0017, Box 44)
    Video files in WMV, MPEG, and DV formats.
  - Miscellaneous photographs, 2001-2007; 23 files; approximately 5 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0003, UA18-01-0001-OP-0004, and UA18-01-0001-OP-0005, Box 44)
  - Nicholas Institute Gala photographs, 2005; 175 files; approximately 325 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0021, Box 44)
  - Nicholas School on Chapel Steps Group photographs, 2011; 6 files; approximately 50 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0034, Box 44)
  - Ocean City photographs, 2006; 93 files; approximately 50 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0014, Box 44)
  - Photo album, 2000 (Box 42)
    Photo album of Nicholas School Board of Visitors, faculty, and staff trip to Yellowstone National Park; Grand Tetons National Park; Jackson Hole, Wyoming; and Wilson, Wyoming, created by Sally Kleberg, Board of Visitors member.
  - Photographs of NSOE dedication and Duke Marine Laboratory, 1996, 1997 (Box 42)
  - Spring Banquet Year in Review Slideshow video, 2005; 1 file; approximatley 775 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0022, Box 44)
  - Stanback Celebration Event photographs, 2011; 142 files; approximately 500 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0036, Box 44)
  - The Nicholas Experience at the Duke Marine Lab event materials, 2007; 61 files; approximately 50 megabytes. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0003, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0018, Box 44)
    Document files in MS Word, MS Excel, and plain text formats.
  - Water Summit photographs, 2009; 326 files; approximately 1 gigabyte. (Digital-materials UA18010001-SET-0004, Optical-disc UA18-01-0001-OP-0015 and UA18-01-0001-OP-0016, Box 44)
- UA2019.0026: Earth and Ocean Sciences (EOS) records, 1
  - EOS Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2011-2008 (Box 43)
    Administrative restriction until 2036. May need additional screening.
  - EOS Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2007-2005 (Box 43)
    Administrative restriction until 2032. May need additional screening.
  - EOS Faculty Meeting Minutes, 2004-2000 (Box 43)
    Administrative restriction until 2029. May need additional screening.
  - EOS Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1999-1997 (Box 43)
    Administrative restriction until 2024. May need additional screening.
  - EOS Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1996-1995 (Box 43)
    Administrative restriction until 2021. May need additional screening.
  - EOS Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1994-1991 (Box 43)
    May need additional screening before use.
  - Department of Geology Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1990-1988 (Box 43)
  - Department of Geology Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1987-1982 (Box 43)
  - Department of Geology Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1981-1977 (Box 43)
  - Department of Geology Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1976-1971 (Box 43)
  - Department of Geology Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1970-1966 (Box 43)